hi welcome back to Long rim and this is
a special session
of question and answer just for the
people who gave us the most support and
at first I'd like to thank you all
for uh signing up for that special level
where you you're actually paying more
so that other people can come and I
always appreciate that
and we're gonna do just a private uh
question and answer for you guys
so Tim you guys ready
yes
so first question guessler is
now that we've learned so much about
bodhichitta and bodies and becoming a
bodhisattva we've learned various
techniques on how to do it I'm feeling a
little overwhelmed about how I'm gonna
enter back into my real life you know
tomorrow I'm gonna go to work
my boss is gonna yell at me everything
is going to go back to quote normal
what are some advices you can give for
us as we're moving out of an intensive
retreat
to then integrate into our real life
yeah that's a good question uh for
example
uh my teacher encouraged me to do later
lateral means normally three weeks four
weeks of retreat
and it would be very difficult for me
because I was the Vice President in the
company
and for me to leave for for one day
was very difficult but to live for three
weeks
and no contact with the office first of
all it was very strange you know
everyone in the company thought I was
crazy
and it was difficult for everybody and I
I remember how difficult it was so uh
then I would go away for three weeks
do my uh you know mantras 100 000
mantras or so
and then I would come back
and it's a good question also after my
three-year retreat
I remember the first day I came out
and I have a close friend named John
Stillwell
and he said get in the car I guess you
know I'm out in the desert for three
years
and he said get in the car and I got in
the car
and he drove me to
McDonald's
and he brought me into McDonald's and he
made me eat french fries
and I
I it was like someone hit me on the head
with a hammer you know it was it was
very very difficult
so I understand the question when you've
been through a deep retreat
and you're going back to your office
then what are you gonna do first my
first advice is
don't expect too much
of yourself you know don't think
that 10 days is gonna make your
bodhisattva
and if you go back to work and you yell
at somebody within 20 minutes
you're a very bad person
because you sat through the whole body
to the retreat
and you you could only keep your body
chitter
for nine minutes
before you yell at somebody at work so
my first advice
you know Dharma people we tend to take
ourselves very seriously you know I'm a
bodhisattva you know bodhisattva has to
be perfect probably I should cut a few
fingers off before the end of the first
day and give them to people you know you
think like that and it doesn't work like
that in real life
uh you're not gonna be much different
after 10 days you have been
the Way You Are
for about a thousand billion lifetimes
then to Think You're Gonna Change
in 10 days you don't be hard on yourself
don't make yourself crazy okay smile
be gentle
with yourself okay be gentle with
yourself we have been
Who We Are
for countless lifetimes
then we're not going to change in 10
days okay but
uh having said that don't be so serious
you know the worst thing in the world
is a very serious nervous Dharma person
you know just relax you're gonna mess up
you're gonna
stop meditating you're gonna miss your
yoga you're gonna
say three bad things
immediately so so don't
don't make yourself crazy Dharma people
who are trying too hard
are unpleasant for everybody
including themselves
Okay so to relax
and take it easy then you'll be a better
buddy summer okay buddy
know how to laugh
at themselves
and they know how to not take themselves
too seriously so just relax
uh but
try to find a way
to make one of these teachings you had a
hundred teachings
you had a hundred different ideas you
had a hundred and twenty pictures I
think
something like that I know because I had
to pick them
and take one just take one so
you are rich
you may not be you know some wealthy
business person or something like that
but you are a diamond Rich you have
hundreds of choices
of practices don't try to practice all
of them
you will get a headache you'll get
grumpy
you'll be worse than when you took the
alarm room okay just relax
I would say take two or three pictures
from all the pictures
and try to practice them at work take
two or three pictures
each day
and make that your theme
at work and then you'll be fine you'll
be fine okay you're not just relaxed and
have fun okay if you're
you are laughing a lot
body Surfers have fun
Buddhist office don't get very serious
but his office don't get nervous about
trying to do everything okay just relax
okay have fun
do the best you can take two or three
pictures to work each day in your head
that's all okay next one
cool so
this is a question about when you were
describing how to do an act of Truth
and then how to load it with bodhichitta
um the question is
should we do this all the time or
won't this consume a lot of our good
seeds because we're doing something very
very powerful all the time and how
should we think about this
that's a good question by the way I Was
preparing for a program for next week
and I was using the Diamond Cutter
Business book the old one and that has a
nice chapter
about active truth so I encourage you to
if you're interested
in Act of Truth
I suggest you you get that book and you
you can study that chapter
and that will talk to you about
how to do an act of truth but
try to appreciate this
an act of Truth for bodhisattva means
if I tried
to be a good person
at work today
then when I get home
my husband should have cooked dinner
right Paul choose something impossible
no just kidding I'm just kidding
you know you can do little acts of Truth
all the time you know uh if it's true
you know I I I worked pretty hard during
the long run retreat
then I hope uh my cousin doesn't argue
so much with my uncle you know you you
can make a little Act of Truth like that
and you are not
using up
your comic Steve
doing the act of Truth
with your old comic seeds makes more
comics days than you use them it's like
a interest on a loan it's like a hundred
and ten percent interest on a loan every
day that goes by you make more money
than what you had in the first place so
if you keep doing little acts of true
you're just making more interest on on
your karma okay you don't lose Karma you
make more karma so acts of truth I think
they're fun
I don't do them too often I kind of save
them for special
occasions when I need something to
happen
which is
might not happen you know I don't know
I hope so and so
I dedicate my karma for the last 10 days
that this person I know who's unhappy
should be happy you know like I I do if
it's true
that I translated from guessler
after he drank coffee and talked too
fast for one hour
uh
and I kept a smile on my face if it's
true
then my friend who's having fight with
her husband or something they should
they should have some peace you know you
can do an act of Truth amen
it doesn't always work okay sometimes
the old seeds aren't too strong
and don't quit you know don't say ah
you know I didn't like the truth
that I don't know
the pizza in my town should get better
and it didn't happen
so I'm gonna quit you know don't be like
that you know don't make impossible
after the truth and then
and then get depressed when they don't
you know do your best do some modest
acts of Truth and and then
get used to it but you're not using up
Karma you are making more karma accept
truth being welcome and I encourage you
to read the chapter in The Diamond
Cutter book about that subject
all right Mr Tim
so here's a question about
when when do karmic seeds get planted so
for example you wrote The Diamond Cutter
book many many years ago
you know best seller translated 30
language Etc
and let's say someone reads it mix it up
today
they go to the bookstore they pick it up
they read it
and then the the way this question is
tied together is about someone's
serving of bodhisattva right
so you wrote the book right and if
someone were to serve you then they get
sort of magic they get seeds from that
from serving it without knowing it
now if they're if they read the book
do you get seeds
good seeds from them reading because
they're bodhisattvas and you helped them
20 years ago when you wrote the book
good question okay good question uh
there's a very there's two interesting
Concepts in the abidharma uh one is
called
and it fascinates me this concept
fascinates me because uh
you know I spent
almost 30 years
serving my teacher you know taking care
of my teacher and and he was tough
and he kept me busy all day I mean he
had the minute you finish one project he
had another project ready and uh it was
hard I'm talking hard projects
like build me a house
you know by yourself and I'm like okay
and uh I did and it was it was so hard a
whole winter building a house in New
Jersey
in uh two-story house
in uh
and then you know I was studying I'll be
Dharma at the same time he was teaching
me abhidharma for 12 years
in the evening and I was building house
and they
this was for eight years before I went
to the diamond business so I I was
working full time for him
and it was
I was building all these buildings and
temples and things like that and then uh
I started to feel
a strangely happened to me I started to
get happier and happier it was really
strange like I would get happier and
happier and happier and I my brain would
expand you know my my study got better
and better in my meditation got better
and better
and then I I always had him to ask
questions he hated
to answer questions he didn't like
questions
and uh
his opinion was
if I taught you for 12 years so far
maybe I covered whatever you're going to
ask me you know so he was he didn't like
questions but I was his driver
and we would go for five six hour trips
to teach he would go teach somewhere so
he was captive in the car he couldn't go
anywhere or on an airplane then I would
ask him questions on an airplane or ask
then sometimes he'd pretend to be asleep
you know
and but finally I would ask him
questions and I said remember to
something strange happened what
I start to feel better and better you
know my mind
is increasing my mental capacity is
increasing and my happiness level is
increasing what is that what's going on
and he said
you built part of the temple in New
Jersey the Mongolian Temple you built a
lot of it you build my house
you know I said yeah but that was like
five years ago you know he said no no
say later means
every time
someone walks in the house you get more
karma
okay every time that we people used to
walk around the house because it was
there was llama in it so they used to do
circumambulation for many hours
he said every time someone goes around
the house that you build
to honor you know the Llama who's inside
the house
then they get like 99 Karma and you get
one percent
because you built a house you know I'm
like wow that's awesome you know
and then he said uh yeah you can study
it now I'll be Dumber and I said well
what happens if I die do I still get the
if I die and people are still walking
around the house later
do I still get one percent he said yeah
you still get one percent I'm like wow
that's awesome you know so
that's called like capital investment uh
Capital Karma investment so if you write
a book
and you get karma from writing the book
but then other people
read it if a new person reads it
after 20 years
then you get interest okay you get
interest from that book
now if you benefit from the book
uh
you know or or if you helped me print
the book or something like that yeah you
get the one percent yeah you also get
one percent
and the nice thing about Dharma
economics
is that everybody gets 100 even if it's
more than a hundred it's like those
dishonest filmmakers who sell points do
you know that
people don't have money to make a film
they give you points say okay you have
three percent of the project you're
going to get three percent of the box
office afterwards that's called points
you know so
there's no limit to the points uh with
the Dharma activity
and yeah
if you benefit from the book
I get one percent you know uh if
and then if I benefit from your benefit
uh you get one percent that's true
that's true it's a nice uh pyramid
scheme Dharma pyramid scheme okay what
do you call that there's a multi-level
Mark MLM it's illegal in China for
example but Dharma MLM is okay
okay Tim
multi-level marketing
[Music]
so a follow-up question to this would be
the idea that if I were to
unknowingly serve coffee to a
bodhisattva and I and I that I get
tremendous seeds from doing so
what about the corollary of
I yell at about a software all right
throw coffee on the bodhisattva or get
angry at the bodhisattva is there an
equal corollary and then what could we
do to be aware of that potential error
we are making yeah good question good
question this is called the walking
across the lawn question
this is called the walking across the
lawn question
and uh there's a thing uh
called yarnet okay your name means uh
for I think three months in the summer
uh Buddhist monks and nuns are supposed
to stay indoors mostly
that's the rainy season the monsoon in
India
and because of the rain there's lots of
bugs
which if you've ever been in India
during months and you can experience
directly direct experience of bugs
and especially bed bugs and so anyway
we're not allowed to walk across a we're
not we're supposed to stay inside
during the rainy season
because we will kill less bugs if we
don't walk across the grass
then uh what's the status
of killing bugs
when you walk across the grass you know
how much karma is that
you don't open the door and say ah I
feel like killing some bugs this morning
you know nobody opens the door and and
says I think I'll go kill some bugs I
think I'll go walk across the lawn right
it's not intentional
so how much karma is it
if you do something
bad but you're not aware of it isn't the
intention
99 of the karma how can you have
why should you do summer retreat
so you don't step on the bus
if you never know you stepped on a bug
and if you didn't want to step on a buck
there's no intention
and there's no awareness of what you did
what if you
throw coffee on them
how much Bad Karma do you get
if you didn't have any intention and you
didn't know they were a bonus offer
right so that's called the answer is
called background radiation okay
background radiation
and I'll I'll give an example okay cat
you know if it rains here
uh
at Diamond Mountain you know
in the theoretical case
that it rained in diamond mountain
uh and you went out for a walk
would you probably kill more bugs with
your feet by accident yeah and she said
yeah and and it's it do you understand
that's statistically
it's more likely that you would kill
more bugs after a big ring and you say
yeah I understand that's enough
intention
to make Karma
okay knowing that it's probable
that something happened
or would happen
is enough intention
to collect Karma okay so that's how we
answer the bodhisattva question okay
what are the chances
that anyone you serve cough is there a
chance okay you made coffee
somebody made coffee this thing else and
Cat I don't know somebody made coffee
this morning
and and you what I call is a background
awareness you have background awareness
it's possible
you know we don't know for sure
but it's possible is is it possible
that anyone you make coffee for
might be a police officer is it possible
yeah and you have that awareness all the
time you never lose that awareness
anytime you make coffee
for anybody
part of your mind
deep down
is aware there could be a buddy stuff
you're aware and anytime you throw
coffee on somebody
part of your mind is also aware
that they could be a bodhisattva and
that much Karma you collect that much
Karma you collect so that can be called
background intention and and it matters
it matters therefore even accidents
uh killing bugs with your car when you
drive your car you do collect Karma why
there's some intention no I didn't want
to kill bugs yeah but you knew you might
right
and that's enough that's enough
intention so
bottom line
coffee for as many people as you can if
they like coffee
and serve people whenever you can
and there's a background possibility
that they might be a buddhistamba now
there's a okay another famous question
if you get angry
you destroy thousands of good seeds the
small print in the contract says
if you get angry at a bodhisattva
you you destroyed lots of seeds that's
the small print in the contract well how
do I know who's a bodhisattva
well how do you know they're not a
bodhisattva well there could be a
buddhistam okay that's enough karma
that's enough intention
to destroy your good seeds if you get
angry at anybody
okay got it so what's a safe thing to do
make coffee for everybody if they like
coffee
and don't get angry at anybody okay you
never know
who's who so it's better to be safe I'll
tell you a beautiful story okay Grandpa
likes stories
so uh
when we started the diamond company uh
we borrowed 50 000 guy fifty thousand
dollars from a guy in London
uh and a Turkish guy in London and we
built the company we built the company
built the company and then I was not uh
I didn't have shares in the coming I
didn't have stock in the company the
stock was held by two people
uh and uh
so
but every year uh we used to have a
meeting and they would split profits you
know they would help share some profits
you know
and uh and I remember we used to go out
for lunch and this was the big meeting
for the year in fact my mama would say
when's the lunch meeting I'd say next
week you'd say good luck good luck
because all the money went to the
monastery you know he's like good luck
good luck you know and then I'd get home
and he'd say did you have the meeting
and say no it's tomorrow I said okay
and then uh they would give me extra
money
for from the prophet
for my Monastery because I was giving
all the money to the monastery so uh
they would
throw in extra money you know
and it got serious it started getting
serious you know like hundred thousand
two hundred thousand they would throw in
extra money you know for the monastery
and there is really they're Jewish you
know
and then finally one day I I they gave
me a huge amount we built a new uh the
background for the monastery a new one
for 3 000 months and and I'm like
I I took the check you know and I said
can I just we're I remember we were out
to dinner at a very exclusive New York
restaurant you know lunch
and uh
and I said can I ask you a question you
know any
he said oh for the Israeli guy he said
yeah what's the the main owner he said
yeah it's a question I said
yes really he said yeah I miss really
I said Israel's 100 Jewish I mean not
even 1999 it's 100 he said yeah we're
100 Jewish she said
well why do you keep giving me money
from my monastery why you keep throwing
in 100 000 to 300 000 why you keep doing
that you know
he said you never know who's right
he says could be the juice could be the
Buddhist could be the Hindus I'm
covering my basis you know when I die
I'm covered you know I give money to
everybody okay why didn't I say that
cover your bases
assume everyone's a bodhisattva okay
then you won't get in trouble
okay cover your bases give coffee to
everybody
and then you cover the few Buddhist
office in the room or or maybe all of
them okay next question Tim
so in this question
is is a segue from assuming everyone's a
bodhisattva
and by having bodhichitta we're so you
know we're love all beings equally
so one could potentially conclude
that we shouldn't get married and love a
single person
because then we may not be loving all
beings equally
how can we think about this seeming
contradiction of loving one person fully
but also supposed to be loving all
beings equally yeah that's a great
question and uh
so when I when I got to University when
I went to Princeton I was a devout
Christian and I was a Episcopal
Christian in um
I wanted to be an Episcopal priest I was
accepted into the priesthood
and uh
the the last year I lived in the
Episcopal churches
quarters I lived in the priest's house
the whole last year uh
in in in the in the University you know
and in the Episcopal Church uh
the priest can marry the priest can get
married you know so I was living with
the priests I knew
who lived in the priest quarters with me
they were all married so there'd be a
special house over there for this priest
and his wife and there'd be special
they always were married you know and
then
I used to watch them you know and I was
curious I was like
it seems like if you're not married as a
as a priest or as a spiritual
counselor you're more available
you know like you don't have to get up
and say I have to go home
you know if someone's having a crisis
uh you can you can focus on them 100 you
don't have to call your wife
you know you can stay at the hospital
all night and and you can serve them so
I was watching them and I was thinking
you know which is better
is it is it better to get married or
it's better not to get married you know
and then I I've had the experience
uh that people I knew who were very
selfish
who seemed very selfish
and then they got married
and then they had children
I had the personal perception
that many of them suddenly became very
sweet people
[Laughter]
I was like wow
you know that having to get up
and change diapers and and feed the
child
you cannot be selfish
and keep that up for very long you it's
gonna break down your selfishness I
guess I think so I mean I've never had
that experience but from observation of
my friends
those who had children
who had to get up at night who had to
who had to break their sleep
who had to warm the bottle who had to
change the diapers who had to get their
hands all poopy
you know for another person uh
they seem a lot nicer or they seem to
have a bigger capacity for love so I I
also used to struggle with this question
you know
is it
should I not have a personal
relationship
because I wouldn't be able to focus on
everyone equally
or should I have a personal relationship
which teaches me to give up what I want
and then I can serve other people better
okay and my conclusion is both are good
okay my conclusion is
do either one that calls to you
and then make it a pop okay turn it into
an opportunity turn it into a path so if
you're attracted to
if you are called
to having a family or having getting
married
without a family either one if that's
your if it calls to you
then do it
and make a pop make it a pop make it an
opportunity
to learn to serve another person
unselfishly okay and or
if you feel called to staying single
and staying by yourself
because it makes you more available to
other people all the time
then follow that one but but in my
opinion after many many years of
watching
married an unmarried priests and other
people
I think both can be useful I think both
can be very useful so I I would say
follow your heart
and see which one calls to you okay and
I think
if you are topkippa
skillful means you can turn either one
into an advantage okay you can be alone
and be more available to people
or you can learn to give up yourself for
your family or for your spouse okay I
think you can practice I think in the
end
every situation
can be used for Buddhist practice it's
up to you it's not the situation it's up
to you
cool
one of the thank you again
one of the concerns that's come up is
what I've been thinking about the 10
benefits of having bodhichitta and
becoming a bodhisattva
there seems to be a potential danger of
causing the negative Pride
we're like I'm a bodhisattva I'm awesome
etc etc right so how can we think about
this and how can we generate this with a
positive sense of pride
and avoid the negative side of it
yeah good okay
I asked my major this so see that
see that all these answers
are really one answer
which is if you find your personal
teacher everything's taken care of okay
if you find your personal
hard teacher
then all the questions are answered
and and if you don't then then you
you're gonna have
you know you
you have to keep asking questions right
so my the mother advice
the big advice
find your personal teacher find your
root Guru you know find your heart
teacher
and and then you can always ask them
questions you know that's the deal so if
you don't feel like you met them yet
then study the mom room
find out the causes
of meeting your rude teacher but you can
guess
it's helping other people connect with
their root teacher so help other people
find their heart teacher
and that will cause you
to find your hard teacher and then all
questions are answered automatically and
and there's no substitute for that
so that's my main advice now
so I'm going to quote my heart teacher
one of my heart teachers uh I asked him
you know
so if I study all this body chill stuff
and if I memorize all these Buddhist
books and I become a great teacher
then isn't there a danger
that I will start to get Pride
you know and actually it will hurt me
you know later
and he said don't worry all right what
do you mean don't move me he says
samsara will take care of everything
I'm like what do you mean he says
samsara will smash your pride in about
10 minutes you know so I said that's not
it don't ask me about that that's not a
problem
will take care of everything you know
the minute you feel like you're doing
well
said Sarah will come and smash
everything so don't worry
have your pride
it's only going to be a
ble to tell you really mess up and you
will destroy your own pride and I was
like Wow remember too that's that's a
hard answer
you know he said don't worry about your
pride
you will screw up so bad because you
have Prime
that you won't be able to be proud about
anything so don't worry we designed
samsara just for you
you know so I'm sorry it's Gonna Knock
You down and fix your friend so go ahead
have your pride it's it's great by the
way I had another advice from another
teacher of mine guessing now on Gilden
who's a great Mongolian Geisha and uh
and I remember
going to him in uh
in his room he I built his room I built
his house
in uh and I went to him and I I said
guess what I have a confession you know
by the way confessions are really good
to do
and they're very uncomfortable
so I went I suggestion I have a
confession
he says what's the confession I said I'm
terribly jealous of another student
who's the student of art you know art
why are you jealous of him his Tibetan
is much better than mine and his
Sanskrit is a thousand times better I
hate him I'm very jealous of him he said
hold on to that jealousy it's great I'm
like what you know I'm waiting for him
to tell me you're a bad person get rid
of your jealousy what's wrong with you
you know you're in it you're living in a
monster and you're jealous of other
people and what's wrong with you you
know and he said great keep going with
that jealousy you know I'm like what he
said it's wonderful
hey I said why he said do you know how
hard you work to try to catch up to him
you know we watch you everybody knows
you're jealous of him by the way it's
not a secret everybody in the monastery
knows how jealous you are and you drive
yourself so hard to keep up with him you
know it's it's wonderful
you know keep up that jealousy and he
says but when you catch up let it go
okay then then let the jealousy go okay
so anyway that seems to be relevant here
by the way I I did catch up maybe but I
didn't get rid of jealousy okay
all right guess in our final question
for today
so it seems that the goal that we've
been taught during this course is that
we want to save all beings from this
samsara that keeps smashing our pride
and our jealousy right or gives us more
of it
um but it seems as though
the world would also based on the
teachings but also be full of many high
bodhisattvas and Buddhas already
that have already become enlightened
right and yes I can see that obviously
there's still work to go because I have
suffering in my life and I see it
but how can we think about this if I see
so much of the suffering around us but
maybe there's
more Buddhas and bodhisattvas than we
thought
how do I kind of put this together
I'm going to quote it's a beautiful
question
and I'm going to quote a famous book
where is this
good yeah here it is
okay I'll say it again
very very famous okay
uh
this is the opening lines of the hata
yoga
okay and they first they give the uh
the the lineage okay
what's it called do you know the lineage
at the beginning of a Hindu book
it's called the parampara
they give the lineage they give who
taught it who practiced it and this is
hata yoga this is called The Yoga of the
Sun and the Moon
uh which is the left and right channels
in the body yoga
okay so yoga and here's the famous verse
okay
this and other Mighty accomplished
beings okay he lists them first like
goraksha and people like that
born into Power by The Yoga of the Sun
and Moon they roamed the universe the
Egg of the pure one what's that
Monday this is the Hindus believed that
the universe is shaped like an egg and
it belongs to Brahma okay they are
wandering the egg
it means they are walking around the
world our world
mingling among the crowds of humans
for they have murdered death itself
they are secretly
these guys who practiced
for many years
and conquered death called dunda right
uh
they are mingling with human beings
secretly they are wandering around Bowie
Arizona
pretending to be normal people okay this
is the opening lines of the yoga by the
way we'll teach this in the yoga Studies
Institute soon
okay we'll go through this book uh
but yeah there's a belief expressed in
this verse
that that
there must if the diamond cut is Sutra
survived
for a hundred Generations
if The Diamond Cutter Sutra
survived for a hundred Generations
if people
did you know your grandfather
Was he alive
he dressed weird right like he dressed
in 1920s or 1930s and he thought it was
cool like geshi Michael still wears long
hair from 1965.
you know there's a generation thing
that uh your grandfather or grandmother
they they think they look good to us it
looks really weird you know on this uh
close from two generations ago and they
gotta have those clothes you know
so
things change
from generation to generation radically
okay clothing hairstyles
morals values when I was young it was
good to meet people from other countries
and try to get to know them
when I was young this was considered the
a beautiful thing to do you know not to
say oh he's from this country I hate him
without meeting anyone from that country
no
you know so uh anyway
uh but certain books
survive
for a hundred Generations you know shoe
Styles hairstyles haircut styles
makeup you know whether you use
blacklistic or purple or you don't use
any
uh it changes radically
from generation to generation but The
Diamond Cutter survives
and you know that big box book
people still working on it still
printing it's still translating it why
it must have worked for somebody
or I wouldn't be here
the those sutras that John Brady is
saving they must have worked for
somebody
or they wouldn't be here okay somebody
must still like long hair or would it be
here right Joe
okay there must somebody must do
got something out of it why am I talking
about that
if The Diamond Cutter survive
for a hundred Generations when haircuts
and shoe Styles don't
it proves that some people must have
gotten enlightened
some people
must have made it to the they must have
become bodhisattvas and they must have
become Buddhists and we just don't meet
them or they're hiding mingling among
the
crowds of humans for they have murdered
death itself okay so yeah definitely
it's a good attitude it's a healthy
attitude
to think about
why did The Diamond Cutter survive
for a hundred Generations
it's because it worked
and some people got to buddhahood
and maybe they are hiding out
at Diamond Mountain driving tractors
stuff like that
and you don't know you really don't know
so that not knowing is a beautiful thing
that not knowing is a very beautiful
place to be okay
all right thank you